Contact

leonardo.jaimovich@gmail.co

www.linkedin.com/in/ leonardojaimovich (LinkedIn) www.espndeportes.com (Other)

Top Skills

Project Management Metodologías ágiles IT Management

Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Azure DevOps Boards for Project Manager

Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate

Aspectos técnicos de los NFTs

DevOps esencial

Scrum Fundation Professional Certificate

Leonardo Jaimovich

Digital Transformation, Service Delivery Manger, IT Consultant Argentina

Summary

My professional goal is to help companies navigate the path to digitization.

My job experience in technology and consulting market began in 1994 in the banking industry. Nowadays my role is Sr Project Manager in Hexagon PPM being part of implementation project through LATAM. Formerly as Delivery Manager in MDE Network responsible for the whole company's delivery area. As Manager at IBM Argentina GBS division, I have participated in numerous SAP implementations and in the development of a variety of software leading the respective teams of development and implementation. My most significant strengths are the ability to achieve an excellent link between the all components and project stakeholders, a strong vocation for teamwork, results orientation, negotiation, and a proactive and creative way to meet the challenges of the market.

Specialties:

- 1.- IT Management & Transformation.
- 2.- People Management.
- 3.- Project Management.
- 4.- Process engineering.
- 5.- ERP implementation.
- 6.- SAP.

Experience

Think and Dev Senior Project Manager July 2021 - Present (3 months)

Hexagon PPM Sr Project Manager October 2020 - June 2021 (9 months)

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Role responsibilities:

Project and Program Management.

Service Delivery Management.

Pre-Sales.

Skillset:

Cross-functional team leadership.

Business analysis.

Software development life cycle.

Software project management.

MDE Network

Senior Service Delivery Manager

August 2015 - October 2020 (5 years 3 months)

Argentina

As Solution Delivery Manager in charge of company operations for the whole product offering. Budget \$6MM.

In charge of the whole company services, my role included responsibilities as follow:

Recruiting process, support to commercial initiatives. People performance process, customer relationship

Management of project and department financial budget.

I began working at MDE when company started, main achievement was to turn it into a profitable consulting team of 15 people.

IBM

Manager

November 2011 - July 2015 (3 years 9 months)

Argentina

Main responsibilities at IBM were full related to project and people management.

I have participated in projects as follow:

Abbvie (Abbot): SAP roll out to an Abbot division (Abbvie)'s spin off. Scope includes RTR, PTP, OTC end to end process. Geographic scope addressed in two waves is Chile, Colombia, Guatemala and México (wave 1) and Argentina, Uruguay, Peru, Ecuador, Panamá, Venezuela, Puerto Rico and Rep. Dominicana (wave 2). Big challenge was working with a tight schedule due to business requirements and to coordinate all countries cultures as well as different operation timing, since legal split has not happened at same time.

Pepsico Foods: template based (on Pepsico International Reference Template model) SAP implementation for Argentina, Uruguay, Chile, Peru, Colombia, Venezuela and Ecuador. Project strategy based on a process reference template where the SAP model is based on. It is a full cycle project, since process definition to go live through construction and SIT, UAT testing stages. Process scope: Finance (AP, AR,CO, COPA), Operation (inventory, production, warehouse management), Commercial (including OTC and DSD). The challenge is to standardize the different sites operation in order to fit them in a unique model. And to integrate SAP to many of the legacy application will stay operational after go live.

Pepsico Flavors (PWF): template roll out for Brazil, Uruguay, Venezuela and Mexico. The project challenge was to put in place a model designed in a previous stage of the project as a template having into account local/legal requirements a full integrated operation between sites. Big ban go live required by our customer and due to its business was other of the team challenges because of the different countries and cultures.

First stage was delivered in Ireland (PWF headquarters), second one in Argentina and Uruguay.

The original go live date was accomplished and we've got an SAP platform running stable in a very short time.

Capgemini

Manager

April 2008 - November 2011 (3 years 8 months)

Argentina

Since I've started working at Capgemini, I was responsible for the project management and involved in cross plataform project (SAP, JAVA, MS). Combining the IT consulting activities as well as process consulting activities. I'm part of a team with professionals from many differents professional roots as well as culture roots.

Those projects are delivered in multinational companies on shore and off shore configuration in many differents industries like Oil and Gas, Agribussines, Retail, Beverage.

I am responsible for business development as bid manager and account manager, depending on opportunities and account demand.

Softtek Argentina
Business Consulting Manager
March 2001 - March 2008 (7 years 1 month)

Argentina

As responsable for SAP implementation projects, being my duty to drive projects team to the global objetives. Manage customer relationships and coordinate the tasks to get the goal.

Formerly, I'm involved in SAP projects, as part of a team. I have performed as an SAP SD consultant for the last two years.

Involved in collecting requirements, analysis, gap analysis, customizing, testing and knowledge transfer tasks.

Before, I was DW project manager. I was in charge of Pre sales, customer relationships and leadership tasks.

Xerox

Consultant

June 1997 - February 2001 (3 years 9 months)

Argentina

Consultant.

I was involved in DW projects (team leader), RRHH projects (Meta 4), and billing project for LA area.

T.G.N

System Engineer

April 1996 - June 1997 (1 year 3 months)

Argentina

Mainly, envolved in re-engineering process. Taken part of an analyst team, aimed to improve all company practices. After that, my responsability was to put on the way all the improvements gap detected in the re-engineering project, evaluating tools, developments and administrative changes too.

Credit Lyonnais Bank System programmer January 1994 - March 1996 (2 years 3 months) Argentina

Involved in mantainance taks, taking part of the capital market support team. Using Oracle developing tools.

Education

Universidad Centro de Altos Estudios en Ciencias Exactas System Engineer, Technology, Business · (1992 - 1996)

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

MBA, Management, Finance, Economic · (2003 - 2005)

O.R.T

Bachelor in Electronic, Electronics Computers. · (1984 - 1989)

Udemy Alumni

Scrum Master - Liderar Equipos Agiles, Project Management · (2020 - 2020)

IAE Business School

Project Management, Ingeniería Posgrados · (2018 - 2018)